<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Webcamoid, The ultimate webcam suite!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://webcamoid.github.io/</id><updated>2019-10-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Webcamoid 8.7.1 released!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/posts/2019/10/22/webcamoid-871-released/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-10-22T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-10-22T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>admin</name></author><id>tag:webcamoid.github.io,2019-10-22:/posts/2019/10/22/webcamoid-871-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bug fixes for Mac and Windows.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;VERY IMPORTANT ADVICE PLEASE READ!!!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; To solve all the bugs mentioned bellow, please remove all virtual cameras and create a new one. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Bug fixes targeting Mac&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This release was specially intended to fix bugs impacting Mac users experience.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first and most important bug to fix was a memory grow that happened when the video frames was sent to the virtual camera but the program in the other side was slow receiving them, what happened was that since the target program was slow, Webcamoid was keep sending the frames, but the frames keep accumulating because the target program was not able to process them. This problem was solved by syncing the frames so now Webcamoid will wait until the frames are processed.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The second problem to solve is that in order to have access to the camera in newer Mac releases the user need to give capture permissions to the program so it can capture from the camera. This problem has been fixed too.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And finally, there has been some experiments trying to bring camera controls support (contrast brightness, gamma, etc.) without much luck. The methods used could conflict with AVFoundation API, so the controls are disabled for now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Bug fixes targeting Mac and Windows&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In older versions of the virtual camera for Mac and Windows, the default frame of the virtual camera plugin was loaded from the resources embedded in the binary, but since the internal resources format was tied to Qt, if Qt changed the internal format of the resources the plugin won't be able to load the resources because the plugin does not make use of Qt.&lt;br&gt;
Instead of doing some hackery to load the frame from resources, the plugins will load the frames directly from file.  &lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="news"></category></entry><entry><title>Webcamoid 8.7.0 released!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/posts/2019/10/01/webcamoid-870-released/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-10-01T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2019-10-01T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>admin</name></author><id>tag:webcamoid.github.io,2019-10-01:/posts/2019/10/01/webcamoid-870-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;On Android port status, fixed camera blinking, many bug fixes and improvements.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Android port keep moving forward&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Webcamoid for Android is nearest that never. Even though Webcamoid is not ready to be used in Android yet, there has been a lot of advances to make it work in the mobile platform. All its basic features are working: camera capture, screen capture, video playback and recording.&lt;br&gt;
The UI still does not play well with small screen devices, this is a pending task that will be solved before the official release.&lt;br&gt;
You can read more at the &lt;a href="https://github.com/webcamoid/webcamoid/issues/169"&gt;Android port&lt;/a&gt; issue. Also, if you feel a bit adventurous you can download and test the APK at the &lt;a href="https://bintray.com/webcamoid/webcamoid/webcamoid/daily#files/android"&gt;daily build&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20191001-1/WebcamoidInAndroid.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20191001-1/WebcamoidInAndroid.png" alt="Webcamoid in Android" title="Webcamoid in Android" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Fixed camera blinking&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you changed the format, resolution or FPS, Webcamoid was turning on and off the webcam quickly many times, if you had a webcam with a led indicator, you can notice the led was blinking many times when you changed the format.&lt;br&gt;
I think this is related to issue &lt;a href="https://github.com/webcamoid/webcamoid/issues/148"&gt;#148&lt;/a&gt;, this bug was probably triggering a hardware bug that did not allowed the camera to recover its normal parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Bug fixes and improvements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many unnecessary plugins were removed like Bin and Probe plugins. Also, unnecessary sub-modules like OSS and QtAudio were removed.&lt;br&gt;
Also, error messages for the virtual camera were improved, making a bit easier to debug problems when installing the virtual camera.&lt;br&gt;
And finally there were fixed some elusive segfaults when switching between effects.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="news"></category></entry><entry><title>Webcamoid 8.6.1 released!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/posts/2019/03/26/webcamoid-861-released/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-03-26T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-03-26T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>admin</name></author><id>tag:webcamoid.github.io,2019-03-26:/posts/2019/03/26/webcamoid-861-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;AppImage icon, fixed Mac and Windows build, fixed man page install.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;AppImage icon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have &lt;a href="https://github.com/TheAssassin/AppImageLauncher"&gt;AppImageLauncher&lt;/a&gt; installed in your system, it can detect and set the icon for the AppImage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Fixes for Windows and Mac&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Users reported that they can't launch Webcamoid in these systems, this bug was fixed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Man page install&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Manual pages are now installed in &lt;em&gt;/usr/share/man/man1&lt;/em&gt; instead of &lt;em&gt;/usr/share/man&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="news"></category></entry><entry><title>Webcamoid 8.6.0 released!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/posts/2019/03/05/webcamoid-860-released/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-03-05T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-03-05T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>admin</name></author><id>tag:webcamoid.github.io,2019-03-05:/posts/2019/03/05/webcamoid-860-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Daily builds, better GStreamer support, many fixes for MacOS.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Test the latest changes with the daily builds&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until 8.5.0 the only way of trying new changes in Webcamoid was &lt;a href="https://github.com/webcamoid/webcamoid/wiki/Raw-build-and-install"&gt;compiling it&lt;/a&gt;, and that means you need to setup a full development environment installing an IDE and configuring it, installing the required libraries, modifying the environment variables and so on. Even when Webcamoid is not that hard to build once you have everything you need, setting up all prerequisites can be overwhelming for non technical users. Otherwise, the only way of testing new things was waiting for a new release, that could take weeks, months or even years.&lt;br&gt;
From now on, you don't need to wait for a new release anymore, you can test all latest changes in the daily &lt;a href="https://bintray.com/webcamoid/webcamoid/webcamoid/daily/link"&gt;build repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Improved GStreamer support&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In older versions when you set GStreamer as recording engine only the primary codecs were enabled, that is the codecs that GStreamer consider well tested, the problem is that many formats and codecs were missing, now the threshold is more relaxed and secondary plugins are supported too, so now you have a broader spectrum of codecs to choose from when recording. Also segfaults and memleaks were fixed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Fixed segfaults and memory leaks in MacOS&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine being working for more than a year in a release, you be tested everything and everything seems to be right and working ok, no problems running the binary packages, but at the moment of uploading the binary packages... baam! users report that they can't launch the program, you check everything and again nothing is wrong. It seems that some incompatibilities related to using a too recent version of MacOS to build Webcamoid caused problems in the target systems. To avoid this problem, from now on all MacOS binaries are build in older MacOS versions.&lt;br&gt;
Finally, a there was a memleak when playing a webcam, a video or the desktop, this bug was also solved.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="news"></category></entry><entry><title>Webcamoid 8.5.0 released!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/posts/2019/01/22/webcamoid-850-released/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2019-01-22T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-01-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>admin</name></author><id>tag:webcamoid.github.io,2019-01-22:/posts/2019/01/22/webcamoid-850-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Reworked virtual camera drivers, UI ported to QtQuick Controls 2, fixed recording bugs.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Virtual camera drivers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the feature that consumed most part of the development time. The virtual camera for GNU/Linux, Mac and Windows was rewritten from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For GNU/Linux, in addition to &lt;a href="https://github.com/umlaeute/v4l2loopback"&gt;v4l2loopback&lt;/a&gt; support, there was also added support for &lt;a href="https://github.com/webcamoid/webcamoid/akvcam"&gt;akvcam&lt;/a&gt; driver. &lt;strong&gt;akvcam&lt;/strong&gt; is an in-house v4l2 driver for Linux designed to offer the same exact features offered by Mac and Windows drivers, like for example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Persistent configuration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Emulated camera controls (brightness, contrast, saturation, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configurable default picture in case no input signal available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are more advantages of this driver, you can check the &lt;a href="https://github.com/webcamoid/akvcam/wiki"&gt;wiki&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20190122-1/VCamInFFandChr.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20190122-1/VCamInFFandChr.png" alt="Virtual camera working in Chromium and Firefox" title="Virtual camera working in Chromium and Firefox" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In previous versions of Webcamoid, the virtual camera for Mac was implemented using &lt;a href="https://github.com/Syphon"&gt;Syphon&lt;/a&gt;, this was far from ideal since the capturing program need to implement a Syphon client and AVFoundation (the default video capture API for OS X) capable programs can't capture from a Syphon server. Since Webcamoid 8.5.0, the virtual camera is implemented as a CoreMediaIO plugin, so now this is can be detected by any AVFoundation capable program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;strong&gt;since OS X 10.14, the virtual camera plugin need to be signed&lt;/strong&gt;, otherwise some programs (mostly from App Store) will not be able to detect the camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Windows virtual camera also received many improvements. Old version was based on DirectShow BaseClasses which had an ambiguous license, so it made quite hard to distribute the code, later Microsoft re-licensed the code of BaseClasses to a clear very well known MIT license, so licensing is not a problem now, but some technical and portability problems still persisted. The code had many problems keeping track of new changes in MSVC and MinGW, it depended on  certain libraries to be loaded dynamically on run-time, 32 bits programs where not able to see the webcam from 64 bits Webcamoid and vice-versa, it was not possible to create more than one virtual camera at same time, and only one instance of Webcamoid was able to send frames to the virtual camera at time. All those problems are solved in Webcamoid 8.5.0.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: many programs based on DirectShow may be able to detect and use the camera, but those &lt;strong&gt;programs based on Microsoft Media Foundation will not work&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can see a full compatibility &lt;a href="https://github.com/webcamoid/webcamoid/wiki/Virtual-camera-support"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;QtQuick Controls 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With Qt deprecating QQC1 it was necessary to port the UI to QQC2, there is not any remarkable visual difference between the old and the new UI, that was only an API change. Some bugs and glitches may appears, but is too late to go back to QQC1 or rewrite the UI completely, despite of this, most of them can be worked around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Recording&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In certain cases when you tried to record a video with audio enabled, it crashed, it happened because the alignment of the samples was not taken into account. In Windows, audio was not recorded at all, this bug was caused because the supported formats were not read and set properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you changed the capture resolution of the webcam, Webcamoid was not aware of the change and it was still recording in the default resolution (640x480 in most cases). Also, default video bit rate is now 1.5 Mbps instead of 200 kbps for better video quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this bugs were fixed with this release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Crash on launch fixed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In some platforms when you tried to run Webcamoid it crashed straightforward, it was caused by certain combination of Qt and the used compiler, the cause is unknown but anyway it was fixed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Microsoft Media Foundation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MMF is the new multimedia framework created by Microsoft and is intended to supersede DirectShow, support for MMF is enabled if you compile Webcamoid with MSVC. MMF is not yet supported in MinGW.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="news"></category></entry><entry><title>Webcamoid 8.1.0 released!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/posts/2017/10/10/webcamoid-810-released/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-10-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-10-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>admin</name></author><id>tag:webcamoid.github.io,2017-10-10:/posts/2017/10/10/webcamoid-810-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Bug fix, binary packages shrinked, added Syphon support for Mac.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Many bug fix&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In previous version there were a problem when audio recording was enabled in which after a few seconds of recording Webcamoid freezed, this problem may be solved and audio recording is enabled by default now.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this version, startup time may be improved after removed unnecessary checks in plugins load. Webcamoid may have a bit slow startup just the first time and load faster in successive runs.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There where many reports of random crashes with almost nothing in common, and I can confirm Webcamoid crashed randomly sometimes, after an exhaustive memory leak scan with Valgrind and Dr. Memory, I found many problems related to how video frames were displayed in the screen, so Webcamoid may be more stable now. Also, enabled linear filtering for frames display.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Mac, screen capture glitched a lot making impossible to do a smooth screen capture recording, this is because Qt uses Cocoa for screen capture, after adding support for AVFoundation in screen capture, the problem was solved.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fixed default install paths for Windows installer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Reduced binary packages size&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time I applied a proper cleaning of debug symbols and unnecessary files, this change is more noticeable for Mac and Windows users. Webcamoid will consume less disc space than before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Virtual camera for Mac through Syphon&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Virtual camera support in Mac is a bit tricky, if you want to share frames with other webcams programs, and do it well, you need to write a kernel extension, and kernel extensions requires signing, and signing requires payment, and at this point is not possible, yet I'm not discarding that option.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So the best solution I've found for now is Syphon for sharing frames with other programs, Syphon is a framework that allow sharing frames as OpenGL textures with other programs also using Syphon. This is More or less a solution for the virtual camera, and I guess most Free Open Source programs will not have problem adding support for Syphon, if they didn't yet, for closed source programs it's a different story.&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="news"></category></entry><entry><title>Webcamoid 8.0.0 released!</title><link href="https://webcamoid.github.io/posts/2017/05/16/webcamoid-800-released/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-05-16T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-05-16T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>admin</name></author><id>tag:webcamoid.github.io,2017-05-16:/posts/2017/05/16/webcamoid-800-released/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mac support, more audio options, more recording options, more flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;h2&gt;Support for Mac&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adding support for Mac was one of the most important ojectives for Webcamoid 8.0.0, since there was not many Free Open Source webcam apps for this platform. I hope Webcamoid can fill the gap for Open Source enthusiasts using Mac, and users of this platform in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/WebcamoidInMac.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/WebcamoidInMac.png" alt="Webcamoid in Mac" title="Webcamoid in Mac" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Support for FreeBSD/TrueOs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few small fixes, Webcamoid is now finally working pretty well in this platform. Webcamoid requires V4L and Linux compatibility layer to be enabled in your system. If Webcamoid doesn't list any webcam, in order to make it work, first you must list your USB devices:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;sudo usbconfig&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;All your webcam devices will be listed as &lt;em&gt;ugenX.Y&lt;/em&gt;, where &lt;strong&gt;X&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Y&lt;/strong&gt; are numbers. And then you must map that device to a v4l device:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="highlight"&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="err"&gt;sudo webcamd -d ugenX.Y -i 0 -v Z -B&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Where &lt;strong&gt;Z&lt;/strong&gt; is the number of V4L device where you want to map the ugen device, so it will appear as &lt;em&gt;/dev/videoZ&lt;/em&gt; in Webcamoid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/WebcamoidInTrueOS.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/WebcamoidInTrueOS.png" alt="Webcamoid in TrueOS" title="Webcamoid in TrueOS" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Improved audio configs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In previous versions only PulseAudio was supported; now Webcamoid supports 4 new systems: ALSA, JACK, OSS and QtMultimedia. And is also possible to select the output and input you want to use for playback and capture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/InputDeviceSelection.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/InputDeviceSelection.png" alt="Input device selection" title="Input device selection" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For each input and output, you can set the sample format, number of channels and sample rate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/AudioDeviceOptions.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/AudioDeviceOptions.png" alt="Audio device options" title="Audio device options" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;More options for recording&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In older versions it was not possible to easily configure codecs and format parameters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/RecordingOptions.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/RecordingOptions.png" alt="Recording options" title="Recording options" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But now each codec offers its own config dialog, ideal for more advanced users who want to fine tune recording.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/CodecOptions.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/CodecOptions.png" alt="Codec options" title="Codec options" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Libraries configs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Webcamoid support FFmpeg and GStreamer for playback, recording, video and audio convertion, but in previous versions, only one of both were available at compile time, so you had to choose between using one or the other. Now, Webcamoid can be compiled with support for both frameworks and the user will be able choose between both at runtime. And not just that, users can also select the audio system and camera capture library.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/LibrariesOptions.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/LibrariesOptions.png" alt="Libraries options" title="Libraries options" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Plugin configs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For developers and more advanced users there is now a new menu for configuring plugins search paths where you can also enable or disable plugins you don't want to load.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/PluginsOptions.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/PluginsOptions.png" alt="Plugins options" title="Plugins options" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Updates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From now on you will be informed if you are using an old or a development version of Webcamoid, so you can be up to date with bleeding edge features and bug fixes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/Updates.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/Updates.png" alt="Updates" title="Updates" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Installers and portables for GNU/Linux&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GNU/Linux users will not need to wait for Weamoid to be packaged for their distros, and they will not need to use an outdated version anymore. Since Webcamoid 8.0.0 you will be able to install it from a nice graphical installer or, if you prefer, run it as a portable program, just make it executable and click it to run.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="img-preview"&gt;
    &lt;a href="/images/20170516-1/GNULinuxBinaries.png"&gt;
        &lt;img src="/images/20170516-1/GNULinuxBinaries.png" alt="GNU/Linux binaries" title="GNU/Linux binaries" /&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><category term="news"></category></entry></feed>